realestateshows.com 2010-12-31

# Real Estate Shows

| 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT    
Real Estate Shows, has created this statement to set forth our policy and commitment to privacy. This statement discloses the information collection and disclosure practices for our Real Estate Shows (the "site"). By accessing the site, you consent to the collection and use of information as described herein. We reserve the right to change our policy and this privacy statement at any time. If we make any material changes to our privacy policy, we will post a new statement on the site and update the effective date set forth above. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy statement whenever you visit the site to see if it has been updated since your last visit.

**Personal Information.** When you register on the site, we will ask you to provide personal information. We collect personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone numbers. We may collect information about your visit to the site, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the site. We may also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every web site you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. 

**Aggregate Information.** Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of users, from which individual user identities have been removed. We collect aggregate information about you and your use of our site and combine it with information about how others use the site. Such aggregate information includes, without limitation, site traffic, page views, and impressions. This information may be correlated to you for our internal use only. However, we may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all aggregate information (i.e., information that does not personally identify you). 

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION    
We use personal information internally to serve our users and to enhance and extend our relationship with our users. We also use personal information to anticipate and resolve problems with our site, to respond to customer support inquiries, and to send you periodic e-mail newsletters which may inform you of enhancements to our site and other products or services offered by Real Estate Shows, to send you relevant survey invitations related to our site and for our own internal operations (including internal analysis as described below). By registering for our Sites or otherwise submitting an inquiry to us you agree to receive the materials described herein. You may unsubscribe at any time from receiving non-service related communications. You should review the following section to understand when we disclose personal information to third parties.

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION   
Except as set forth in this privacy statement, we do not disclose, sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personally identifying information collected at our Sites to any third party. We will disclose personal information in the following circumstances:

**Internal Analysis and Operations.** We will use and disclose information about you for our own internal statistical, design or operational purposes, such as to estimate our audience size, measure aggregate traffic patterns, and understand demographic, user interest, purchasing and other trends among our users. We may outsource these tasks and disclose personal information about you to third parties, provided the use and disclosure of your personal information by these third parties is restricted to the performance of such tasks. We may also share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. We require our third party vendors to keep such information confidential and to only use the information for the purpose it was provided. We are not, however, legally liable for third party violations of our policies. 

**Transaction Processing.** We will disclose personal information to one or more third parties, as necessary, to provide you with the services. As stated above, your personal information is forwarded to one or more third party service providers (such as a credit card processing agency, or posting on Realtor.com) in order to provide you with the services. Service providers may contact you to complete the transactions you have requested by any methods available to him or her including via e-mail, telephone, regular mail, in person visits or other means. _We do not regulate how these third party service providers use or disclose your personal information and are not responsible for removing your information from any third party lists. Please contact the third party service providers directly to be removed from their lists._

**Protection of Real Estate Shows and Others:** We disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this privacy statement or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety; or to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, our Sites; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. 

**Business Transfers.** In addition, information about users of our Sites, including personally identifiable information provided to us by our users, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of the company.

**Co-Branded Services.** Some services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Real Estate Shows and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services. 

LINKS  
Please be aware that we may provide links to third party Web sites from our site as a service to our users and we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites. We have no ability to control the privacy and data collection practices of such sites and the privacy policies of such sites may differ from that of Real Estate Shows. Therefore, we encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of such sites before providing them with any information.

COOKIES  
We may use cookies to identify users and customize their experience on our site based on information they give us. Cookies are small pieces of information or files that are stored on a user's computer by the Web server through a user's browser for record keeping purposes. A cookie itself is not designed or intended to read any information from your computer (other than the contents of the cookie); rather, it is an identifier used by the Web site that originally placed it on your hard drive. The actual contents of the cookie information can be retrieved by the same site's Web server in order to personalize, monitor, or regulate the use of the site.

SECURITY  
We use reasonable security measures to store and maintain personally identifying information to protect it from loss, misuse, alternation or destruction by any unauthorized party while it is under our control.

CHILDREN  
We do not intend, and our site is not designed, to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly solicit data from children, and we do not knowingly market to children. If you are under 13 years old, you should not register for our services or otherwise provide information on our site.

QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our site, or your dealings with our site, please contact us at the following address or email us at info@Real Estate Shows.

|
